<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Od samego rana</title>
    <description>by Antonio Valdez Arce
</description>
    <link>http://antonio.3manaties.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://antonio.3manaties.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2014 20:25:52 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2014 20:25:52 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Test deployment</title>
        <description>&lt;h2&gt;Testing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deployment OK&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2014 21:24:25 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://antonio.3manaties.com/blog/test/2014/11/08/deployment-test/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://antonio.3manaties.com/blog/test/2014/11/08/deployment-test/</guid>
        
        <category>test</category>
        
        <category>deployment</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>test</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mexican stereotypes: Big Family</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As a mexican living abroad i find it funny when i hear stereotypes about us and our country. So with this post i start a series of mexican stereotypes and will give my opinion (objective opinion of course) about wether they are true or false.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What they say: Mexican families are huge!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All around i hear this and also jokes about it. But i can&amp;#39;t say it&amp;#39;s a lie. Taking my family as an example, from my father&amp;#39;s side i have 7 uncles and 2 aunts and from my mother&amp;#39;s side 3 uncles and 5 aunts. This gives me an unknown number of cousins as every uncle and aunt have at least 3 children. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a Whatsapp group with my cousins (father&amp;#39;s side) and there are more than 50 memebers on the list, meaning the number of cousins at an age of having a phone. Everyday i wake up in the morning and i find more than 100 unread messages, it&amp;#39;s amazing :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All my family is spread around the country, so there are members i don&amp;#39;t know yet and i have to admit, some others that i would not recognize if i met them on the street. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, i like to have such a big family, i&amp;#39;m just proud of it when people get surprised by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Veredict:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;True stereotype&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 19:30:25 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://antonio.3manaties.com/blog/mexican/stereotypes/2014/11/07/big-family/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://antonio.3manaties.com/blog/mexican/stereotypes/2014/11/07/big-family/</guid>
        
        <category>stereotypes</category>
        
        <category>mexico</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>mexican</category>
        
        <category>stereotypes</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here We go!</title>
        <description>&lt;h2&gt;It&amp;#39;s decided&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Antonio is blogging!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok already, enough with the fancy third person, I finally created my first blog and we&amp;#39;ll see if I can keep up with the content. My plan is to post from time to time things i do or think to share them with family and friends. Also i will try to write some things related with my profession just for myself, it&amp;#39;s just easier to learn if I land stuff in some place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it&amp;#39;s done, I already blogged!, I&amp;#39;ve started, this is my first post and the &lt;a href=&quot;/assets/images/cover-izmir.jpg&quot;&gt;cover picture of the blog&lt;/a&gt; is from our trip to Turkey in 2007, the Izmir main square was so colorful and warm that day. I used my old Lomo camera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check more info about this blog going to the &lt;a href=&quot;/about/&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nara!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 14:34:25 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://antonio.3manaties.com/blog/lifestyle/2014/10/05/here-we-go/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://antonio.3manaties.com/blog/lifestyle/2014/10/05/here-we-go/</guid>
        
        <category>lifestyle</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>lifestyle</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
